Liam Christensen

022 621 6727 | LiamJChristensen@gmail.com | 297 Ravensbourne Rd, Ravensbourne, Dunedin 9022

Personal Information

I am a recent graduate of a Bachelor of Information Technology from Otago Polytechnic. I have experience working in professional I.T. environments but mostly in operations roles and I would like to pivot to a developer position. I enjoy learning new technologies and being a part of an effective team.

Experience

I.T. SUPPORT OFFICER | FARRA ENGINEERING LTD | OCT 2018 - CURRENT

Sole provider of part-time in-house I.T. Support.

- Day-to-day I.T. responsibilities
- Maintaining and upgrading servers and computers
- Communicating with external providers

I.T. TECHNICIAN | REMARKIT SOLUTIONS LTD | NOV 2017 - FEB 2019

Working as an I.T. technician providing support and deploying hardware.

- Managing I.T. deployments
- Providing troubleshooting and technical support to clients
- Large scale, company-wide device installation

Education

BACHELOR OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY | OTAGO POLYTECHNIC | JUNE 2020 CERTIFICATE OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY L4 | OTAGO POLYTECHNIC | JUNE 2017

Skills & Qualifications

- Service IQ Customer Service Award
- Certified in Comprehensive First Aid
- Current Driver License

References

David Rozado
Principal Lecturer – Otago Polytechnic
David.Rozado@op.ac.nz

Warren Bailey Southern Region Manager – Remarkit Solutions Warren.Bailey@remarkit.co.nz Ph. 021 273 282 Michael Holtz
BIT Team Leader – Otago Polytechnic
Michael.Holtz@op.ac.nz

Other Experience

PEER TUTORING | OTAGO POLYTECHNIC | APR 2018 - JUNE 2020

Teaching I.T. skills and topics to other students.

- Quickly building and developing relationships
- Creating specialized teaching materials for students
- Efficiently teaching new information

FRUIT PICKING | DARLINGS ORCHARD | DEC 2016 - FEB 2017

Summer Job picking and thinning fruit in Central Otago.

- Very physical work
- Working as part of a team
- Time management and working to a deadline

Interests

- Mountain Biking
- Spanish

- Guitar
- Swimming